What else do you think we could add to the course program to help with this reading problem?
你们认为我们在课堂项目上可以加点什么来解决阅读问题呢？
There's not really anything because it's my problem.
没有什么，因为这是我的问题。
I remember we were given long articles to read.
我记得我们曾经要读长篇文章。
We didn't like that but now I realise that reading those long articleswas good preparation for the things I need to read now.
我那时不喜欢，但是现在我意识到读长篇文章对于我现在的阅读是一种很好的准备。
Also,in class we regularly had speed-reading tasks to do, and we kept a record of our reading speed, so the teachers were encouraging us to work on that.
另外，我们在课上定期会有快速阅读要做，我们对阅读的速度计时，因此老师鼓励我们这样做。
That's true Spiros,but what we read could have been different.
没错，Spiros，但是我们读得本可以不同。
Sometimes in the English class I felt frustratedwhen I had to read articles about the environment or health or education,
有时在英语课上，当我读环境、健康或教育的文章时，我总感到受挫，
because I wanted to concentrate on my own field, but we didn't read anything about engineering.
因为我想专注于我的领域，但是我们读不到任何关于工程学的文章。
So,I think I wasted some time learning vocabulary didn't need
所以，有时我觉得我在浪费时间学一些我用不着的词汇。
But surely the strategies you were taught for dealing with that vocabulary were helpful
但是教你处理词汇的方法肯定是有用的。
Yes,but psychologically speaking, I would have felt much better working on reading from my own field. What do you think Spiros?
是的，但是从心理上说，我更喜欢读自己领域的文章。你觉得呢，Spiros？
I agree;that would have helped my confidence too and I would have been more motivated.
我同意，这也会提高我的自信心，使我更有动力。
It was good though that we could work on our own topics when we wrote the research assignments.
当我们写研究作业的时候，这对于我们研究的题目也有帮助。
Okay,let's move on to writing now ...
好的，现在谈谈写作……